Inventory of the Thomas Hill collection
Hoover Institution Archives
Thomas Hill collection
circa 2000-2009
2011C60
Hill, Thomas, collector.
9 manuscript boxes (4.5 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Pamphlets, brochures, leaflets, flyers, and other ephemeral printed matter, relating to political, social and environmental issues in Germany, and to German foreign relations and development assistance.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives in 2011.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Scope and Content of Collection
Pamphlets, brochures, leaflets, flyers, and other ephemeral printed matter, relating to political, social and environmental issues in Germany, and to German foreign relations and development assistance.
Note: if no date is listed on the inventory, the materials are undated, but assumed to be within the 2000-2009 date range
Arrangement
Arranged alphabetically by organization name or general category
Collection Contents
- AGEH (Engagement der Arbeitsgemeinschaft für Entwicklungshilfe e.V.), 2008-2009 (Folder 1: 1)
- AEJ (Arbeitsgemeinschaft der Evangelischen Jugend in Deutschland e.V.) (Folder 1: 2)
- Africavenir, circa 2009 (Folder 1: 3)
- Alcohol/Tobacco/Drug Prevention, 2009 (Folder 1: 4-6)
- Amnesty International, 2009 (Folder 1: 7)
- Archiv3 (Folder 1: 8)
- ARiC (Antirassistisch Interkulturelles Informationszentrum ARiC Berlin e.V.) (Folder 1: 9)
- ASW Aktionsgemeinschaft Solidarische Welt e.V., 2000-2009 (Folder 2: 1)
- ATTAC (Association pour une Taxation des Transactions Financières pour l'Aide aux Citoyens, 2005-2010 (Folder 2: 2-4)
- Berlin (Gays, Lesbians, AIDS), 2009 (Folder 2: 5-6)
- Berlin (Gays, Lesbians, AIDS), 2009 (Folder 3: 1-2)
- Berliner Entwicklungspolitischer Ratschlag (Folder 3: 3)
- Bundesministerium für Wirtschaftliche Zusammenarbeit und Entwicklung (Folder 3: 4)
- Café Libertad (Folder 3: 5)
- CBM Christoffel-Blindenmission (Christian Blind Mission), circa 2007-2008 (Folder 3: 6-7)
- DAAD (Der Deutsche Akademische Austauschdienst e.V.) (Folder 3: 8)
- DED (Deutcher Entwicklungsdienst), 2003-2009 (Folder 3: 9)
- Deine Stimme Gegen Armut (Folder 3: 10)
- Deutsch-Afrikanische Gesellschaft e.V. (Folder 3: 11)
- DGVN (Deutsche Gesellschaft für die Vereinten Nationen e.V.) (Folder 3: 12)
- EED (Evangelische Entwicklungsdienst e.V.), Nov. 2004, June 2009 (Folder 4: 1-2)
- Ein Ende der Armut (Folder 4: 3)
- Environment and Ecology, German NGOs, 2005-2009 (Folder 4: 4)
- Environment, Ecology Germany (Folder 4: 5)
- EPIZ! Globales Lernen in Berlin (Entwicklungspolitisches Bildungs-und Informationszentrum e.V.) (Folder 4: 6)
- EXILE (Kulturkoordination e.V.) (Folder 4: 7)
- FDCL (Forschungs-und Dokumentationszentrum Chile, Lateinamerika) (Folder 4: 8)
- Freie Universität Berlin (Folder 4: 9)
- Gemeinsam für Afrika, 2006 (Folder 4: 10)
- General Multiple NGOs (Folder 4: 11)
- German government, 2009 (Folder 4: 12)
- Greenwatch, 2007-2009 (Folder 5: 1)
- GSE (Gesellschaft für Solidarische Entwicklungszusammenarbeit), 2005 (Folder 5: 2)
- GTZ (Deutsche Gesellschaft für Technische Zusammenarbeit) (Folder 5: 3)
- Humboldt Foundation, 2008 (Folder 5: 4)
- IJGD (Internationale Jugendgemeinschaftsdienste) (Folder 5: 5)
- Informationsbüro Nicaragua (Folder 5: 6)
- INISA (Initiative Südliches Afrika e.V.) (Folder 5: 7)
- Inwent (Folder 5: 8)
- Inkota, 2008-2009 (Folder 5: 9)
- Kolumbienkampagne Berlin (Folder 5: 10)
- LIDL (Lidl Lohnt Sich nicht für die Arbeiterinnen) (Folder 5: 11)
- Make It Fair, Nov. 2007-March 2009 (Folder 5: 12)
- Medica Mondiale (Folder 5: 13)
- Ministries of agriculture and environment, Germany, 2009 (Folder 5: 14)
- MISEREOR Ihr Hilfswerk, 2007-2009 (Folder 6: 1-2)
- Mission Einewelt (Folder 6: 3)
- Le Monde Diplomatique (Folder 6: 4)
- Nomos (Folder 6: 5)
- Oikocredit, 2008-2009 (Folder 6: 6)
- Oxfam, 2004-2009 (Folder 6: 7)
- Political counterculture, Germany, various NGOs (Non-governmental organizations) (Folder 6: 8)
- Political counterculture, Germany, various NGOs (Folder 7: 1-4)
- Political Counterculture, Germany, various NGOs (Folder 8: 1-2)
- PTB (Physikalisch-Technische Bundesanstalt) (Folder 8: 3)
- RAA Berlin (Regionale Arbeitsstellen für Bildung, Integration und Demokratie e.V.) (Folder 8: 4)
- SODI (Solidaritätsdienst-international e.V.), 2009 (Folder 8: 5)
- Stiftung Nord-Süd-Brücken, 2008 (Folder 8: 6)
- Survival (Folder 8: 7)
- TID (Tibet Initiative Deutschland e.V.), 2007-2008 (Folder 8: 8)
- UNESCO (United Nations Educational, Scientific and Cultural Organization) (Folder 9: 1)
- Unfair Tobacco (Folder 9: 2)
- United Nations (Folder 9: 3)
- Unknown flyers (Folder 9: 4)
- UNO Flüchtlingshilfe (Folder 9: 5)
- Welt Sichten, June?August 2009 (Folder 9: 6)
- Welt Weit Wasser (Folder 9: 7)
- UNHCR (United Nations High Commissioner for Refugees), 2008 (Folder 9: 8)
- Venro, 2007-2009 (Folder 9: 9)
- Vereinte Nationen, 2007-2008 (Folder 9: 10)
- WFD (Weltfriedensdienst e.V.), 2007 (Folder 9: 11)
- World Bank, 2009 (Folder 9: 12)
- WFP (World Food Program) (Folder 9: 13)
- ZFD (Ziviler Friedensdienst) (Folder 9: 14)
- Zeit zu Sprechen (Folder 9: 15)
- Zukunft Lo(c)kt (Folder 9: 16)